# IDOWU ADIGUN

Badagry, Lagos · 09071554045
Idowumichael2509@gmail,com · LinkedIn Profile · Twitter/Blog/Portfolio

Enthusiastic web developer knowledgeable and skilled with Java Script and React. I have demonstrated good use of my skill by developing pixel perfection UIs and integration of third party APIs. I love problem solving and standing up to challenging task to create a solution. I have worked on several projects this includes, landing pages, weather app, To do List, a chess plugin and many more.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

OCT 2021 – DEC 2021 FRONTEND DEVELOPER, ZURI CHAT.

Fixing of bugs

AUG 2021 - OCT 2021

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER, HNGI8 INTERNSHIP

- Implementation of user interfaces
- Consumption of APIs
- Built a chess plugin with my team for a chat app

MAY2020 - OCT2020

FRONTEND DEVELOPER, GOOGLE AFRICA DEVELOPER SCHOLARSHIP.

- UI/UX Implementation
- Integration of third party APIs

## **EDUCATION**

**SEPT 2016- AUG 2021** 

### **B.ENG MECHATRONICS, BELLS UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY**

- Second class honors (upper division)
- Project work: analysis of F450 autonomous drone

**SEPT 2010 – JULY 2016** 

O'LEVELS, NIGERIA INTERNATIONAL SCHOOL

Laboratory prefect

#### SKILLS

- Html and css
- React
- Git and GitHub

- Java Script
- Creative thinking
- communication